<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <archivalAbstracts>
        <archivalAbstract id="M18867">
            <colTitle>The Morris Dickstein Papers</colTitle>
            <colAbstract>Morris Dickstein is a distinguished humanities professor, American cultural historian, and widely published author and critic. The Morris Dickstein papers contain correspondence with fellow academics and prominent literary figures, as well as drafts and research files for many of Dickstein's books, essays, reviews, and lectures.</colAbstract>
        </archivalAbstract>
        <archivalAbstract id="M1126">
            <colTitle>Gay Men's Health Crisis records</colTitle>
            <colAbstract>The Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), America's oldest AIDS organization, formed in 1982, serves to educate the public about HIV/AIDS, provide care services for People with AIDS (PWAs), and advocate at all levels of government for fair AIDS policies. It is a volunteer-supported, community-based organization that provides programs to clients and members of the general public regardless of HIV status, gender, or sexual orientation. The records document the three aspects of GMHC's activities and contain correspondence, memoranda, minutes, pamphlets, photographs, posters, questionnaires, reports, surveys, video recordings, and other material. The bulk of the collection consists of correspondence, memoranda, and reports regarding GMHC's safe sex education programs and client services.</colAbstract>
        </archivalAbstract>
        <archivalAbstract id="M6196">
            <colTitle>The September 11th Fund records</colTitle>
            <colAbstract>The September 11th Fund (2001-2005) was established by The New York Community Trust
			and the United Way of New York City to meet the immediate and long-term needs of victims, families,
			and communities affected by the terrorist attacks of September 11th, 2001. The September 11th Fund
			records hold general administrative files and program-related files created through the funding of grants
			for such needs as cash assistance, employment assistance, health care, and mental health.</colAbstract>
        </archivalAbstract>
		<archivalAbstract id="M6141">
            <colTitle>The 9/11 United Services Group records</colTitle>
            <colAbstract>The 9/11 United Services Group was formed in December 2001 to facilitate, expedite and enhance coordination of services among various charities and agencies in the aftermath of the September 11th terrorist attacks. The September 11th Fund, the American Red Cross, the Salvation Army, and Safe Horizon were responsible for spearheading this collaborative charitable response after recognizing the need for coordinated service. The 9/11 United Services Group records hold administrative files, service coordination files, and files from the Ongoing Needs Study and the Framework for the Coordinated Delivery of Social Services in Future Major Emergencies report. There are also documents outlining the group’s Financial Advice Referral Program and files documenting its work with victim advocacy and community relations.</colAbstract>
        </archivalAbstract>
		<archivalAbstract id="M1">
            <colTitle>The Gumshoe Jr Test records</colTitle>
            <colAbstract>This is the abstract of the Gumshoe Jr Test records. It was created to test the Gumshoe Jr application and does not say much</colAbstract>
        </archivalAbstract>
    </archivalAbstracts>